itduzzit.com 2015-06-16

# itDuzzit - Privacy Statement

Itrios LLC (hereinafter itDuzzit.com) takes your privacy seriously. We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting itDuzzit.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

itDuzzit.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://www.itduzzit.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us [here](http://www.itduzzit.com/duzz/contact-privacy). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

itDuzzit.com complies with the U.S. â€“ E.U. Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union member countries. itDuzzit.com has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view itDuzzit.comâ€™s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/ . 

## What Personal Information Does itDuzzit.com Gather?

Here are the types of information we gather:

  * **General Information You Give Us:** When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address, and store any information you enter on itDuzzit.com or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.
  * **Authentication Information You Give Us:** You may choose to use itDuzzit.com to make connections to accounts you have in other applications. Typically, you will need to provide authentication information that enables itDuzzit to connect to these applications on your behalf. itDuzzit.com stores authentication data you enter for your other applications, and you may subsequently update, changed, or delete the authentication data you have entered. Once you have authenticated to another application, itDuzzit on your behalf may have access to retrieve and modify data in that application.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us, including your IP address, cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page being requested. 
  * **E-mail Communications:** We may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from itDuzzit.com if your computer supports such capabilities.
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to your account information.

## We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order(s)
  * Send you order confirmation(s)
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product update notifications
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by logging into www.itduzzit.com with your itDuzzit.com username and password, clicking on "Account", and then clicking on "Cancel Account".

## What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. itDuzzit.com sets and accesses itDuzzit.com cookies on your computer. This enables itDuzzit.com to recognize you and your browser, and to enable you to access duzzits and data that you have created on itDuzzit.com.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, as cookies are required by itDuzzit.com, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to use the site.

## Does itDuzzit.com Share the Information It Receives?

itDuzzit.com is not in the business of selling information about our customers to others. We share information only as follows:

  * **itDuzzit.com Partners:** We may provide information to trusted partners working on behalf of or with itDuzzit.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that itDuzzit.com or substantially all itDuzzit.com assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Protection of itDuzzit.com and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law such as to comply with a subpoena; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of itDuzzit.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

itDuzzit.com may display targeted advertisements based upon personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria. itDuzzit.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted advertisement. If you wish not to have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads. However, by interacting with or viewing an advertisement, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the advertisement.

## How Secure Is Information About Me?

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

itDuzzit.com works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us [here](http://www.itduzzit.com/duzz/contact-privacy). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?

itDuzzit.com may include third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites.

These third-party Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our Web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

itDuzzit.com may also display personalized third-party advertising based on personal information about customers. Although itDuzzit.com does not provide any personal information to advertisers, advertisers (including ad-serving companies) may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized advertisement meet their criteria to personalize the ad (for example, users in the northwestern United States).

## Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

Customers may update, change, or delete their registration information by editing their user / account record. To update your registration information, or to cancel your account, please login to http://www.itduzzit.com with your itDuzzit.com username and password and click "Account". Customers may update, change, or delete authentications to other applications. To update your connected application authentications, please login to http://www.itduzzit.com with your itDuzzit.com username and password and click "Connections". To discontinue your account and have your registration information deleted, please email support@itduzzit.com. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

## Are Children Allowed to use itDuzzit.com?

itDuzzit.com is intended for people 18 and over. We will not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If it comes to our attention that a user has revealed, on itDuzzit.com, that they are under 18, their account will be immediately closed.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here as well as by email prior to the change becoming effective. 

## Blogs

itDuzzit.com offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@itduzzit.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at support@itduzzit.com.

## Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, you can contact us at:

Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues   
Itrios LLC   
2334 W Lawrence Ave, Suite #216   
Chicago, IL 60625
